<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<didyouknow>
	<dyk>
		Sound travels almost 5 times faster underwater than in air.
	</dyk>
	<dyk>
		Sponges hold more cold water than hot.
	</dyk>
	<dyk>
		An iguana can stay under water for 28 minutes!
	</dyk>
	<dyk>
		You begin to feel thirsty when your body losses 1% of water.
	</dyk>
	<dyk>
		Hot water freezes faster than cold water.		
	</dyk>
	<dyk>
		A banana contains 75% water.
	</dyk>
	<dyk>
		Rain contains vitamin B12.
	</dyk>
	<dyk>
		Cucumbers are 96% water.
	</dyk>
	<dyk>
		A jellyfish is 95% water.
	</dyk>
	<dyk>
		Hippopotamuses are born under water.
	</dyk>
	<dyk>
		Giraffes can't swim!
	</dyk>
	<dyk>
		An elephant's trunk can hold over 5 litres of water.
	</dyk>
	<dyk>
		There are no rivers in Saudi Arabia.
	</dyk>
	<dyk>
		The water in the Dead Sea is so salty that its easier to float than sink.
	</dyk>
	<dyk>
		Armadillos can walk underwater!
	</dyk>
	<dyk>
		Dolphins can hear underwater sounds from over 20km away!
	</dyk>
	<dyk>
		The typical wave height from Pacific tsunami is between 6 - 9 metres.		
	</dyk>
	<dyk>
		A rat can tread water for 3 days.
	</dyk>
	<dyk>
		Dolphins can dive to a depth of almost 1km in 2 minutes.
	</dyk>
	<dyk>
		Snakes can't bite in water (they would drown otherwise).
	</dyk>
	<dyk>
		Gorillas can't swim!
	</dyk>
	<dyk>
		Canada has more lakes than any other country!		
	</dyk>
	<dyk>
		Blood is 6 times thicker than water.
	</dyk>
	<dyk>
		Sheep won't drink from running water.
	</dyk>
	<dyk>
		Camels can drink 94 litres (25 gallons) of water in less than 3 minutes.
	</dyk>
	<dyk>
		A cabbage is 91% water.
	</dyk>
	<dyk>
		The first drug that was sold as a water soluble tablet was aspirin in 1900.
	</dyk>
	<dyk>
		8.5 million tons of water evaporates from the Dead Sea every day.
	</dyk>
	<dyk>
		Rice is grown on paddies to kill weeds.
	</dyk>
	<dyk>
		The average shower temperature is 38˚C (101˚F).
	</dyk>
	<dyk>
		Raindrops are not actually tear shaped.
	</dyk>
	<dyk>
		The average human drinks over 16,000 gallons of water in a lifetime.
	</dyk>
	<dyk>
		Flushable toilets were in use in ancient Rome.
	</dyk>
	<dyk>
		Sea water is approximately 3.5% salt.
	</dyk>
	<dyk>
		Water is a bi-product of burning.
	</dyk>
	<dyk>
		Sun light can penetrate clean ocean water up to a depth of 73m.
	</dyk>
	<dyk>
		Less than 1% of Earth's water is available for drinking.
	</dyk>
	<dyk>
		Giraffes and rats can last longer without water than camels.
	</dyk>
	<dyk>
		When water freezes it expands by 9%.
	</dyk>
	<dyk>
		The "Pacific" ocean is the peaceful ocean.
	</dyk>
	<dyk>
		After Hawaii, New York is the state surrounded by the most water.
	</dyk>
	<dyk>
		Lake Superior (Ontario) has more water than the other four combined.
	</dyk>
	<dyk>
		Great Bear Lake (NWT) is the largest lake entirely within Canada.
	</dyk>
	<dyk>
		Antarctica has as much ice as the Atlantic Ocean has water.
	</dyk>
	<dyk>
		Many fish change sex during the course of their lives. 
	</dyk>
	<dyk>
		The water needed to create a laptop equals nearly 70 loads of laundry. 
	</dyk>
	<dyk>
		A gallon of water weighs 8.34 pounds. 
	</dyk>
	<dyk>
		At 1 drip per second, a faucet can leak 3,000 gallons per year. 
	</dyk>
</didyouknow>